hello everyone welcome to this talk on
大家好，欢迎来到
spring boot and IntelliJ ID before we
Spring Boot和IntelliJ ID，然后我们
start I would like to ask a few
开始我想问几个
questions so first question is was using
问题，所以第一个问题是使用
spring boot already okay that's fifty
spring boot 已经可以了五十
percent who is using IntelliJ ID that's
使用IntelliJ ID的百分比
fifty percent so the those who are not
百分之五十，所以那些不是
using IntelliJ what are you using are
使用IntelliJ您正在使用什么
you using eclipse osts yeah sorry
您使用eclipse osts是的，对不起
netbeans I have one guy using a war
netbeans我有一个使用战争的家伙
military oh so you're the guy using
军事哦，所以你是那个家伙
NetBeans okay no sorry so my name is
NetBeans好的，不好意思，我叫
Tiffany Cole I'm working for pivot alum
蒂芙尼·科尔（Tiffany Cole），我正在为枢纽明矾工作
I'm working on the spring boot project
我正在从事Spring Boot项目
and this is my friend young yeah my name
这是我的朋友，年轻人，是我的名字
is John Simm Arabic for jetbrains and
是约翰·西姆（John Simm）的阿拉伯语，代表喷气机
I'm responsible for the spring and
我负责春天
spring boot a framework support in
Spring Boot中的框架支持
IntelliJ IDEA right so let's get started
正确的IntelliJ IDEA，让我们开始吧
with a lot of slides right that's it all
带有很多幻灯片，仅此而已
right so you already knew about status
对，所以您已经知道状态
pringle I owe you get an extensive demo
我欠你一个广泛的演示
yesterday other keynote or if you were
昨天其他主题演讲，或者如果您是
to this the spring cloud session this
到这个春季云会议这
morning on extensive showcase of that so
上午在广泛的展示，所以
I'm not going to show you that again but
我不会再告诉你，但是
what's really interesting is if you're
真正有趣的是，如果您
using IntelliJ ID you can basically
使用IntelliJ ID，您基本上可以
interact with that service right away
立即与该服务互动
right from the ID so I'm going to create
直接从ID，所以我要创建
a new project that we're going to use
我们将要使用的一个新项目
today so I'm going to select create new
今天，所以我要选择创建新的
projects from initializer then I can
从初始化的项目，然后我可以
choose which to which service I want to
选择我想要的服务
connect two if by by any chance you have
如果有机会，请连接两个
your own customization of start of
您自己定制的开始
spring delay or actually you could do
春天延迟或实际上你可以做
that but i'm just going to use the
那，但我只是要使用
regular service for it i'm going to just
定期的服务，我要去
keep the default not making the job of
保持默认状态不起作用
this wall joke i guess you already heard
这个墙开玩笑，我想你已经听到了
that before I'm keeping all those
在我保留所有这些之前
default is fine I'm going to use the
默认是好的，我将使用
latest and we don't have I don't want to
最新的，我们没有，我不想
focus too much time on spring boot
将太多时间集中在 spring boot 上
itself so I'm
本身，所以我
to create very quickly a simple
快速创建一个简单的
application so i'm going to use security
应用程序，所以我要使用安全性
web GPA for some reason we made that
Web GPA出于某种原因，我们认为
joke again I know H to the actuator
再次开玩笑，我知道执行器的H
because it's cool what did I miss oh
因为很酷，我想念什么哦
let's proposed test right notta and I'm
让我们提出测试正确的notta，我是
going to call that spring one demo so if
打算打电话给那个春天一个演示，如果
you do that basically what you get is
你基本上做到了
you get a project so it's actually
你有一个项目，所以它实际上是
contacted contacting started spring no
接触接触开始弹簧否
deal with the things that you've
处理你所拥有的东西
configured downloading the project
配置下载项目
extracting the project where you've
将项目提取到您所在的位置
decided and set up everything so what
决定并设置所有内容
we're going to do today because you may
我们今天要去做，因为你可能
have heard about the spring boot
听说过 spring boot
supporting into j-14 this is IntelliJ 15
支持j-14，这是IntelliJ 15
EAP with some patches that I received
EAP，我收到了一些补丁
yesterday unless we on the bleeding edge
除非我们处于最前沿
shape so consider that IntelliJ 15
形状，所以请考虑IntelliJ 15
snapshot so if everything breaks yeah
快照，如果一切都中断了
you know it right well anyway I want to
无论如何我都想知道
show you what's new in today in IntelliJ
向您展示IntelliJ中的最新消息
IDEA 15 so that if you're using IntelliJ
IDEA 15，因此，如果您使用的是IntelliJ
14 you can you can see the difference so
14你可以看到差异，所以
the first thing that's new here is the
这是新的第一件事是
project got created automatically so you
项目是自动创建的，因此您
don't have to refresh it or ask to
不必刷新或询问
import the maven pump it's basically
导入Maven泵，基本上
done automatically the new thing also is
自动完成的新事物也是
that you get a run configuration created
您将创建一个运行配置
out of the box so you can stop you up
开箱即用，可以阻止您
immediately and the last thing which is
立即，最后一件事是
new intelligence if teen is that the
新的情报，如果青少年是
spring fight the spring face at sorry is
春天打架，春天的脸对不起
auto detected so you don't have to
自动检测到，因此您不必
create it and we'll come to that later
创建它，我们稍后会谈到
so very quickly I'm going to create a
所以我很快就会创建一个
domain model
领域模型
for speaker so i have that prepare for
演讲者，所以我有准备
you the content is not very interesting
你的内容不是很有趣
right it's just a simple GP entity a
对，这只是一个简单的GP实体
repository that's here as well using
也在这里使用的存储库
spring data you've probably seen that in
spring data ，您可能已经在
the past and I want to make sure that I
过去，我想确保我
have instances in my data store every
每个实例都在我的数据存储区中
time I start so I'm going to use some
我开始的时间，所以我要用一些
speakers here so important sequel if you
讲者在这里很重要的续集，如果你
don't know about that it's a it's a
不知道这是一个
feature from having it which basically
从基本上具有的功能
allows you to run any sequel statement
允许您运行任何续集语句
that you want when the schema is created
创建架构时所需的
so if i stop that then i get a nap with
所以如果我停止了，那我会睡个午觉
a bunch of a bunch of features so let's
一堆功能，让我们
see what we have here oh right so i need
看看我们这里有什么，哦，所以我需要
to login i added the security starter so
要登录，我添加了安全启动器，因此
i need to be able to login and what
我需要能够登录以及什么
springwood does it creates a default
springwood会创建默认值吗
user called user anybody knows what the
用户称为用户，任何人都知道
password might be no wrong so the
密码可能没错，所以
password is generated every time the
每次生成密码
application start that's really really
应用程序启动真的是真的
much matter and oh that's true laughs
重要的是，哦，这是真正的笑声
that stuff then I have my speakers
那东西，然后我有我的扬声器
created here right so that was easy very
在这里创建的，所以很容易
fast so this password is actually going
快速，因此该密码实际上正在使用
to be generated at every run so it's
每次运行都会生成，因此
going to change every time I stop the
每次我停止时都会改变
app and it's made in such a way that
应用程序，其制作方式
there's no way you can remember it so we
您无法记住它，所以我们
have to we'll have to fix that on also
必须我们还要修正它
to show you quickly the inflowing point
让您快速了解流入点
which for now is empty but we're going
现在是空的，但我们要去
to fix that yeah so let's see how
解决这个问题，让我们看看如何
IntelliJ IDEA can help us
IntelliJ IDEA可以帮助我们
customizing that app so the first thing
自定义该应用程序，因此第一件事
for those who don't know that at all
对于那些根本不知道的人
probably not much in the audience anyway
反正观众人数可能不多
is spring boot as a very rich
spring boot 非常丰富
configuration model so when you use auto
配置模型，所以当您使用自动
configuration and you want spring boot
配置，你想 spring boot
to change slightly the way the auto
改变汽车的方式
configuration is supplied you can
您可以提供配置
customize it with configuration keys and
使用配置密钥对其进行自定义，然后
one of the problem with those
这些问题之一
configuration key is is that you have to
配置关键是您必须
remember them all you have to find them
记住他们，找到他们所需要的一切
by a google the documentation or stack
通过谷歌的文档或堆栈
overflow whatnot so what those guys have
什么都没溢出，那些家伙有什么
built in IntelliJ IDEA is content
内置IntelliJ IDEA的内容
assistance right in the IE based on the
IE中基于
configuration that is available in new
新的可用配置
project so I want to change the password
项目，所以我想更改密码
so let me type pass and then I get
所以让我输入pass然后我得到
content assistance about the options
有关选项的内容帮助
that are available to me and you can see
可供我使用，您可以看到
that i can see that the name of the key
我可以看到钥匙的名称
obviously some documentation and the
显然一些文档和
type so let's say I'm going to say
输入，所以说我要说
change me and that will change my
改变我，那会改变我
default the default password for the
default的默认密码
default user the next thing I want to
默认用户我想做的下一件事
say is I went to click on that one by
说是我去点击那个
the way when I had the the
当我有的方式
authentication papa it told me that the
认证爸爸告诉我，
real was spraying because that's the
真正在喷涂，因为那是
default value and I want to change that
默认值，我想更改它
so i type real i can see the default
所以我输入真实我可以看到默认
value there were no no default value for
值没有默认值
the password but there is for this one
密码，但是有一个
so i can see directly writing gie what
所以我可以看到直接写什么
the default value for that key is and
该键的默认值为
I'm going to say something like ello and
我要说类似ello和
I'm going a feature from boot witches
我要从女巫那里走
random property souls I'm going to say
我会说随机属性的灵魂
give me a number between 0 and 5 and use
给我一个0到5之间的数字并使用
that as a whale obviously that's
作为一条鲸显然是
completely stupid but it's just to show
完全愚蠢，但这只是为了展示
you that the integration with property
你与财产的融合
sauce in Antigua idea is pretty deep
安提瓜的想法酱很深
then I want to change the role of my
然后我想改变我的角色
user so I tapped role and i can see that
用户，所以我点击了角色，我可以看到
i have this security user the troll
我有这个安全用户巨魔
icons we can't see that because the
图标，我们看不到，因为
phone is bigger but actually
手机更大，但实际上
it's a list so if i do that i get
这是一个列表，所以如果我这样做我会得到
basically support for this based access
基本上支持基于此的访问
i'm going to say it's also admin so that
我要说这也是管理员
i can still access to dl actuator
我仍然可以使用dl执行器
endpoint but i can also create any kind
端点，但我也可以创建任何种类的端点
of icky i want right so let's say i'm
我想要正确的，所以可以说我是
going to create food counter which does
将要创建食品柜台
not exist and the I details that tell
不存在，我告诉的细节
you so immediately I don't know about
你，所以我不知道
that key and I'm going to use that in
该密钥，我将在其中使用
the info on point so I'm going to say
点的信息，所以我要说的是
info for those who don't know info is a
对于那些不知道信息是
map and we take every key of that map
地图，我们将获取该地图的每个键
and we expose that indian foreign point
我们揭露了印度的外来点
so basically if you have info that foo
所以基本上如果你有信息foo
equals something then you'll have an
等于某物，那么你会有一个
entry foo equals something in d for
条目foo等于d中的某项
endpoint what you would use typically is
终结点您通常会使用的是
you're going to expose the name of the
您将要公开的名称
service the version of the service or
提供服务的版本或
any metadata that you want to expose so
您想要公开的任何元数据
if you want a quick example of that
如果您想要一个简单的例子
because spring dot io is a spring booth
因为spring dot io是spring的展位
application so if i go on the inflowing
应用程序，所以如果我继续流入
point then I get this so that's the
点，那么我明白了，那就是
typical information that you would
您将要提供的典型信息
expose right yeah
暴露是的
come again yeah don't for in point is
再次来，是的，不是因为
the jacket area yeah so what we're going
夹克区是的，所以我们要去
to do is we're going to say counter and
要做的是我们要说反
we're going to reuse our key and we can
我们将重用我们的密钥，我们可以
see that we have also links between keys
看到我们在键之间也有链接
I can see that the value would be 42 and
我可以看到该值为42，
I can say oh yeah I forgot to mention
我可以说哦，是的，我忘了提
that you can see that the the key is in
你会看到钥匙在
a special highlight just to show you
一个特别的亮点只是为了向您展示
that it's actually the key of a map and
它实际上是地图的关键，
the key entry delicate and finally as we
关键条目微妙，最后像我们
will see later yell is going to showcase
稍后会看到大喊大叫
that we also have additional support for
我们也有额外的支持
special keys so for instance we have one
特殊键，例如，我们有一个
in spring boo that's logging the level
在春季嘘记录水平
you can see that it's a map and
您可以看到它是一张地图，
basically it you can use that to tune
基本上你可以用它来调整
the logging configuration regardless of
日志配置，无论
the logging system that you're using so
您正在使用的日志系统
there you get basically two smart auto
那里基本上有两个智能自动
completion for that you get small to the
完成，因为你变得渺小
completion for the key right and you
完成关键权利，您
also get small total completion for the
也为
value and we'll come back to that later
值，我们稍后再讲
in this presentation all right there's a
在此演示文稿中，有一个
typo all right missing thank you then if
错字没事，谢谢，然后如果
i restart that i'll have to login
我重新启动，我必须先登录
obviously again i just want to show you
显然再次，我只想告诉你
that everything works as as expected so
一切都按预期工作
first of all i get this auto
首先，我得到这个自动
configuration report because I flip the
配置报告，因为我将
auto configure package to debug so
自动配置软件包以进行调试
that's the first effect then if I go
那是第一个效果，如果我走
back to my service it says hello to
回到我的服务说你好
that's the random value and change me
那是随机值，改变我
and then basically I have this bar and
然后基本上我有这个酒吧
whatever right but the point I'm trying
不管什么权利，但我要尝试的要点
to make here is ok these are maybe not
在这里可以确定这些可能不是
the customization that you're looking
您正在寻找的定制
for but if you're working with a spring
但是，如果您正在使用弹簧
good application and you want to figure
良好的应用程序，你想图
out what kind of options you have you
你有什么样的选择
can you can type a few character in that
您可以在其中输入几个字符吗
file and
文件和
figure out basically live what kind of
弄清楚基本上住什么样的
functions you have you also get
您拥有的功能也会得到
validation out of the box as long as you
只要您开箱即用进行验证
activate the validate on built which is
激活内置的验证
in this section so compiler validation
在本节中，因此进行编译器验证
validate on build so what's new in 15 is
在构建中进行验证，因此15中的新功能是
the spring five-set is created
春季五件套创建
automatically for you or to detect it
自动为您或检测它
for you so you know this food counter is
为了你，所以你知道这个食物柜台是
is unknown so it basically tell me so
未知，所以它基本上告诉我
here down below I don't know about that
在这下面我不知道
key and if I put some crap so this is
关键，如果我放些废话，这是
obviously not an index and I try to
显然不是索引，我尝试
restart my app then if one we start it's
重新启动我的应用程序，然后如果我们启动它
telling me basically okay there's
告诉我基本上可以
something wrong in your config file so
在您的配置文件中有问题，所以
please fix that you can you can
请修复您可以的问题
obviously decide whether or not you want
显然决定你是否想要
to run those validations but if you
运行那些验证，但是如果您
activate that it's pretty ending like
激活它的漂亮结局
all right take over and I want to show
好吧，我想展示
you some of the stuff which is coming
您一些即将到来的东西
and spring boot 103 there's a whole lot
和 spring boot 103还有很多
of new metadata introduced into spring
春天引入的新元数据集
good one or three and the IDE can
一三个很好，IDE可以
actually make use of that metadata to
实际利用该元数据来
enhance the completion navigation we
增强完成导航功能
just saw for some of those keys in
刚刚看到了其中的一些钥匙
IntelliJ 14 we had some manual mapping
IntelliJ 14我们有一些手动映射
of some known keys to some known type or
某些已知类型的某些已知密钥或
to some known behavior for that key and
该键的一些已知行为
that has been generalized and can be
可以概括为
used from the metadata which is built or
从构建的元数据中使用或
packaged into the spring boot
包装到 spring boot 中
distribution so any IDE can make use of
发行版，因此任何IDE都可以利用
that information for the user so the
为用户提供的信息，因此
first thing I'm going to show you is
我要告诉你的第一件事是
enhanced support for deprecating keys so
增强了对弃用密钥的支持，因此
when I start and type some
当我开始输入一些
key part name which contains some
关键部分名称，其中包含一些
deprecated keys you will see on the
您将在
bottom of this completion list the
此完成列表的底部
deprecated keys are sorted automatically
不推荐使用的键会自动排序
to the last position because it's most
到最后一个位置，因为它是最
unlikely to be used up early and if I
不太可能用尽，如果我
choose such a key you see the
选择这样的钥匙，你会看到
highlighting in the editor it's strike
在编辑器中突出显示它是罢工
true so you see immediately that your
是的，所以您立即看到您的
application for example after upgrading
升级后的应用程序
to a newer version of spring boot is
到较新版本的spring boot是
using a deprecated or no deprecated key
使用不推荐使用或不推荐使用的密钥
and it also tells you in the top up here
它也告诉您这里的充值
and what is new in spring boot 103
以及 spring boot 103的新功能
metadata is that not only can you
元数据不仅可以
duplicate a key but you can also define
复制密钥，但您也可以定义
just just font size here a so-called
只是这里的字号
replacement key so we see that this key
更换钥匙，所以我们看到这个钥匙
is deprecated and we have a reference to
已弃用，我们有一个参考
the null current key or the updated key
当前键为空或更新后的键
which you should be using so you can go
您应该使用哪个，以便您可以去
and change that manually but that's
并手动更改，但这就是
stupid because we already know about it
愚蠢的，因为我们已经知道了
and we all know our favorite shortcut
我们都知道我们最喜欢的快捷方式
which is all danger to trigger an
这都是引发危险的危险
intention or quick fix in IntelliJ and
意图或快速修复IntelliJ和
we'll use the new intention to replace
我们将使用新意图替换
that he do the new replacement key and
他做了新的替换密钥，
we are done that's the stuff about
我们完成了有关
application we can also add metadata
应用程序我们还可以添加元数据
about the reason for this deprecation so
关于这种弃用的原因，所以
you can tell the user why that
您可以告诉用户为什么
application was introduced into the
应用程序被引入
police there is known here because we
警察在那里是众所周知的，因为我们
screw up the name so we didn't know that
搞砸了这个名字，所以我们不知道
you know okay another area which was an
你知道吗，另一个区域是
ain't is support for given value lists
不支持给定的值列表
so if you have some property which is a
所以如果你有一些财产是
string type value it's it's not type so
字符串类型值，不是它的类型
usually you want to provide a list of
通常您想提供一个清单
known values for that key and that is
该键的已知值，即
not possible in
在不可能
the Springwood 123 release metadata and
Springwood 123发布元数据和
one example of this is this key which
此密钥的一个示例是
has a list of known values which are
有一个已知值列表
valid for this configuration key and we
对于此配置密钥有效，我们
enhanced also the documentation view for
还增强了文档视图
keys with non value lists you can see
您可以看到带有非值列表的键
this table here on the left side the
这张桌子在左边
values which are valid and on the right
有效值在右边
side there's a description which is also
旁边有一个描述
stored in a metadata of spring boot to
存储在spring boot的元数据中
give you some hints about what this
给你一些提示
value is going to trigger at runtime and
值将在运行时触发，并且
you also see the documentation here in
您也可以在此处查看文档
the completion proverb so it's very easy
完成谚语，所以这很容易
to figure out what that value is going
弄清楚该价值将如何发展
to do at runtime another big improvement
在运行时要做的另一项重大改进
is a building support from sorry for I
对不起，我是一个建筑支持
should mention by now that ian is
现在应该提到ian是
actually typing on the French al today
实际上今天在法国人身上打字
yeah which is kind of weird but I'm
是的，这很奇怪，但我
trying to so please bear with me while I
试图让我在我身边忍受
try to find the keys for enums so in
尝试找到枚举的键，所以在
terms of course have a fixed set of
当然有固定的一组
values you know Castle fields which are
你知道的值城堡领域是
valid and this key refers to an enum
有效，此键引用一个枚举
acknowledged mode in this case which has
在这种情况下的确认模式
the values which are automatically
自动的值
proposed now in the completion pop up
现在建议在完成弹出
here again you can see the documentation
再次在这里您可以看到文档
which is actually taken on the fly from
实际上是从
the Javadoc of the CM so even if you
CM的Javadoc，即使您
have like your own configuration keys
有自己的配置键
and you refer to some enum property and
并且您引用了一些枚举属性和
since you're a good developer you will
既然您是一名优秀的开发人员，您将
have written some Java doc on that
已经写了一些Java文档
anyone can figure out what this enum
任何人都可以弄清楚这个枚举是什么
value is going to do and again the same
价值将要做，并且再次相同
value lists and overviews available in
可用的值列表和概述
the documentation view here as well I
这里的文档视图
mean it's basically the same thing as a
表示与
fixed set of manually defined values
固定的一组手动定义的值
again value and description taken from
再次取值和描述取自
Java doc
Java文档
very easy to understand and to provide
非常容易理解和提供
content assistance for your users of
为您的用户提供内容帮助
your boot and extension okay and that's
你的启动和扩展好了，那就是
not a child which is now treated
不是现在接受治疗的孩子
specially our configuration properties
特别是我们的配置属性
referring to a glass so let me find one
指着玻璃杯，让我找到一个
spring data source type for example and
spring数据源类型，例如和
the documentation tells us that this is
该文档告诉我们，这是
a fully qualified name of the connection
连接的完全限定名称
pool implementation springwood should be
池实施应是
using it's usually auto detected but
使用它通常是自动检测到的，但是
just for demonstration purposes just key
仅用于演示目的
is a very nice demo control space and
是一个非常好的演示控制空间，
you get automatically filtered list of
您会自动过滤出以下列表
completion proposals of any class
任何课程的完成建议
matching the required base class data
匹配所需的基类数据
source in that case and you can just hit
在这种情况下，您可以点击
return and be done one thing to mention
返回并做一件事要提
is wherever you have some value which
无论您拥有什么价值，
refers to package or to a class or
指包装或类或
something like that it fully supports
完全支持的东西
refactoring so anytime you change your
重构，因此无论何时您更改自己的
class or references which are used in
类或用于
the values here in your configuration
您配置中的值
files will be reflected automatically
文件将自动反映
for you so it really understands the
为你，所以它真的了解
connection between classes packages
类包之间的连接
whatever and the declaration of that
随便说什么
right
对
I'm sorry okay so yeah so the question
对不起，好吧，是的，这个问题
yeah so the question was how do we find
是的，问题是我们如何找到
out about these values how do we know
关于这些价值观，我们怎么知道
what to propose right we are going to
我们将要提出什么建议
look at that in a few minutes when we
几分钟后看一下
take a look at the actual metadata
看一下实际的元数据
behind all this magic and we are going
所有这些魔术背后，我们要去
to add some demo about this okay right
添加一些关于这个好的演示
another thing which is quite common is
另一件事是很常见的
content type for example and here you
例如内容类型，在这里您
get a full list of known which is
获取已知的完整列表
content types so it's very easy to
内容类型，因此很容易
choose the one you want the data screen
选择一个您想要的数据屏幕
media tight Bailey if you wonder right
媒体紧Bai的贝利，如果您想知道正确的话
so that will be there automatically for
这样就会自动存在
any property which is of that type and
该类型的任何财产，以及
the similar thing is available for
类似的东西可用于
encoding so maybe you need or want to
编码，所以您可能需要或想要
set some encoding for example for
设置一些编码，例如
sending mails or whatever and here again
发送邮件等等
you get the full list of known encodings
您将获得已知编码的完整列表
so it's very easy to provide completion
因此提供完成非常容易
for that as well what if we change the
为此，如果我们改变
banner right yeah so everyone last
正确的旗帜，所以每个人都最后
spring boot banner on the front
前面的春季引导横幅
especially up front or friend josh and
特别是在前期或朋友乔什和
the spanner can actually be changed so
实际上可以更改扳手，因此
maybe you want to have your company
也许你想拥有你的公司
banner or the banner of your project
标语或您项目的标语
you're working on and that's very easy
你正在努力，这很容易
to do so the property for that is banner
这样做的属性是横幅
dot location and it has a default value
点位置，它具有默认值
of a class pass resource so this is
类通过资源，所以这是
actually a spring io resource reference
实际上是Spring io资源参考
or property which can be modified by you
或您可以修改的属性
so let's do it let's add our own banner
所以让我们添加自己的横幅
and I'll just let's call it spring one
我就叫它春天一
for example
例如
so spring 160 I'm going to create the
所以160年春天我将创建
fire and the class pass
火和上课合格
and stefan was nice enough to prepare a
而斯特凡足够好准备
life template with a great-looking
美观的生活模板
spring one logo and as you would expect
弹出一个徽标，正如您所期望的
by now intellij knows that this is a
到目前为止，intellij知道这是一个
reference to class password source of us
参考我们的班级密码来源
navigation completion and again of
导航完成并再次
course refactoring so any spring IO dot
课程重构，因此任何春季IO点
resource type will be handled in the
资源类型将在
same way automatically if you have such
如果你有这样的方式自动
configuration properties in your own
自己的配置属性
metadata right didymus no that's ok be
元数据正确，没错，没关系
able to showcase the yellow format yes
能够展示黄色格式是
the young informant is something new and
年轻的线人是新事物，
IntelliJ 15 be careful it's still a work
IntelliJ 15请注意，这仍然是一项工作
in progress it has some known quirks I'm
在进行中，我有一些已知的怪癖
going to work on them very soon many
很快就要为他们工作
people ask about it so we had to do
人们问这个，所以我们不得不做
something because for unknown reasons to
因为未知原因
me some people prefer Yama so let's
我有些人喜欢Yama，所以让我们
increase the font size yeah so basically
增加字体大小是的，所以基本上
you get the exacting the completion as
你得到严格的完成
you would expect in again we are using
您会期望我们再次使用
the same metadata here it's just an yong
相同的元数据，只是一个永
it said again you can control click here
它又说你可以控制点击这里
go to the definition of this key
转到此键的定义
shoulder documentation of the ski it's
滑雪的肩膀记录
more or less the same level of
大致相同的水平
application properties but still it has
应用程序属性，但仍然具有
some things which are missing yet but we
有些东西还不见了，但我们
really want to have the same level year
真的想有同年级
so you have to have free choice of
所以你必须自由选择
whatever configuration format you prefer
您喜欢的任何配置格式
in your projects right so we still got
在您的项目中，所以我们仍然
this yellow bug are you yeah food
这个黄色的虫子你是食物吗
counter that right yeah it has a nice
反对那是的，它有一个不错的
value but still spring boot or rather
值，但仍然是 spring boot
IntelliJ tells me that it doesn't know
IntelliJ告诉我不知道
anything about it which is clear because
关于它的任何事情都是显而易见的，因为
all the other keys we've been using now
我们现在使用的所有其他键
in the configuration file
在配置文件中
have some kind of metadata behind it so
背后有某种元数据，所以
now we are going to look at how this
现在我们来看看
magic is going to happen right so there
魔术即将发生，所以那里
has been a quick fix already in IntelliJ
已经是IntelliJ中的快速修复
14 to define such additional metadata
14定义这样的附加元数据
which is basically some men your way to
基本上是一些男人
define configuration keys and give them
定义配置键并给他们
some magic so again all enter is your
一些魔术，所以再次进入都是你的
best friend and we have a quick fix to
最好的朋友，我们可以快速解决
define this configuration key which is
定义这个配置键是
not to be found in the existing method
在现有方法中找不到
metadata yet so there are some rules
元数据，所以有一些规则
behind us such additional metadata must
在我们后面，这些额外的元数据必须
be defined in a file called additional
在称为“附加”的文件中定义
spring configuration metadata of JM and
JM和
it shall be stored in a resources route
它应存储在资源路由中
in your project we don't have such file
在您的项目中，我们没有这样的文件
so IntelliJ ask me whatever I want to
所以IntelliJ问我想做什么
create this file and offers me a list of
创建此文件并向我提供以下列表
known resource routes so we only have
已知的资源路线，所以我们只有
one year so i'm going to create it here
一年，所以我要在这里创建
and this is basically the match behind
这基本上是后面的比赛
all this configuration key completion
所有这些配置密钥完成
navigation and stuff like that it's
导航之类的东西
basically metadata stored and jason and
基本上存储了元数据，杰森和
we will take a look at what exactly can
我们将看看到底能做什么
be or must be defined here so the first
在这里或必须定义，因此第一个
thing is of course the name property so
事情当然是name属性，所以
it has to have a unique name type will
它必须具有唯一的名称类型
define the type of this configuration
定义此配置的类型
key we are going to change it here
关键，我们要在这里更改它
because 42 is obviously or rather a
因为42显然是
number than a string maybe again auto
数字比字符串也许再次自动
completion for refactoring as a port
完成重构为端口
here as well and then there's this key
这里也有这把钥匙
description and IntelliJ already
描述和IntelliJ已经
provided some dummy text for us and
为我们提供了一些虚拟文字，
that's one funny thing here description
这是一件有趣的事情
text has some rules behind it just like
文字后面有一些规则，就像
Java doc the first sentence will be used
Java doc将使用第一句话
for short description and that is the
简短说明，这是
short description we previously saw in
我们之前看到的简短描述
the auto completion list when when we
自动补全列表
had a completion for anon values for
完成了的负值
example where it took
例子花了
the first sentence of the javadoc to
javadoc的第一句
just show it as quick documentation and
只需将其显示为快速文档即可
the full documentation would be shown in
完整的文档将显示在
the full java in and then full
完整的Java然后完整的
documentation view for what we had with
我们所拥有的文档视图
the value and description table so since
值和说明表，因此
there are some rules to that we can
有一些规则，我们可以
trigger it it's maybe a bit hard to see
触发它可能很难看
here on the Beamer but there is an error
在Beamer上，但是有错误
now we don't have a dot after the first
现在我们在第一个之后没有点
sentence and IntelliJ reminds us to to
句子，IntelliJ提醒我们
have this door after the first sentence
第一句话后有这扇门
so that the IDE can extract a use useful
这样IDE可以提取有用的使用
first Creek documentation so what else
第一份Creek文档，还有什么
can we define here quite a few things
我们可以在这里定义一些事情吗
actually a little value default value
实际上有点值默认值
would be the next thing or we saw some
会是下一件事，或者我们看到了一些
properties which have a default value
具有默认值的属性
like for example the banner location we
例如横幅位置
did as lasting again this is auto
做了一样持久，这是自动的
completion here IntelliJ knows what can
在这里完成IntelliJ知道可以
be here in this metadata and what not at
在此元数据中，什么不在
work position so we are going to set 42
工作位置，所以我们要设定42
I'm sorry
对不起
i dled yeah there are some rules to this
我向是的，对此有一些规定
metadata they are undefined in the
元数据，它们在
spring root reference documentation so
Spring root参考文档
if you if you go to the Supreme good
如果你去最高的地方
documentation reference you'll have a
文档参考，您将拥有
section an advent section that basically
基本上是一个出现部分
tells you how you can deal with that
告诉你如何处理
stuff yeah and if you if you're
是的，如果你是
wondering at this point if you guys have
想知道在这一点上你们是否
to write that by hand for every single
为每个人手写
property that you have it's probably a
你拥有的财产可能是
nightmare right nobody does that so
噩梦吧，没人这样做
we're going to show you how you can
我们将向您展示如何
generate that automatically but just for
自动生成，但仅用于
completeness because sometimes and
完整性，因为有时
particular we do there is each case
特别是在每种情况下
where you can't use the automated way
无法使用自动方式的地方
for some reason so we needed a way to
由于某种原因，所以我们需要一种方法
also be able to specify the manually we
也可以手动指定
actually use that extensively in spring
实际上在春季广泛使用
boot itself so we're going to show you
自行启动，我们将向您展示
that now and after we're going to show
现在和之后，我们将展示
you what you're really supposed to use
你真正应该使用的东西
it right but that clarifies how it works
没错，但这澄清了它的工作原理
behind the scenes okay hopefully so
在幕后好吧希望如此
there's a couple more of properties just
还有一些属性
a quick reference we have deprecation so
快速参考，我们已弃用，因此
we saw that in action before I can give
在我付出之前，我们已经看到了行动
it a reason for the application so you
这是申请的原因，所以你
want to duplicate my content no okay
想复制我的内容，不好
just showcasing thank you and as we saw
只是展示谢谢，正如我们所见
there is the possibility to specify with
有可能用指定
replacement key again we have Auto
再次更换钥匙，我们有自动
completion here and again we have Auto
完成一次又一次，我们有自动
completion here to refer to the other
完成这里参考其他
key we want the user to use in the
我们希望用户在
future of course this is all unnecessary
未来当然这是不必要的
for our demonstration so I'm going to
为了我们的示范，所以我要
delete that and maybe you notice this
删除它，也许您会注意到这一点
rate a red banner on top of the editor
在编辑器顶部给红色横幅打分
it's a bit too small to read on the
它太小了，无法阅读
screen it says spring boot configuration
屏幕上显示Spring Boot配置
annotation process are not frowned on
注解过程不皱眉
class pass so
班级通行证
the question is how does this Jason get
问题是这个杰森如何得到
processed into something we can use in
处理成我们可以使用的东西
the IDE or at runtime to use this
在IDE或运行时使用此功能
metadata and as you would guess there's
元数据，而且您会猜到
an annotation processor involved in this
与此相关的注释处理器
magic which will take our additional
魔法将带走我们的额外
spring config metadata process it in
spring config元数据处理它
some way mix it with some other way if
以某种方式将其与其他方式混合，如果
the phone is going to demonstrate after
电话将在之后演示
me and generate the metadata we actually
我并生成我们实际上的元数据
are going to use in the IDE so this is
将要在IDE中使用，所以这是
the source file format for metadata for
元数据的源文件格式
manual metadata it will get transformed
手动元数据将被转换
into something slightly different but
变成稍微不同的东西
not too different so we have to fix this
没什么不同，所以我们必须解决这个问题
let's go to our maven it would be so
让我们去我们的行家吧
nice if i could do I dental dam banner
如果我能做的话，我很高兴牙科坝横幅
in it would definitely for me and yes
肯定会适合我，是的
see me would be nice and it will be done
看到我会很好，这会完成的
okay he said it would be done so it we
好吧，他说会做到的，所以我们
thought that you know no yeah
以为你不知道
so we have to find this spring boot
所以我们必须找到这个 spring boot
configuration processor add it as a
配置处理器将其添加为
dependency and since it's an annotation
依赖关系，因为它是一个注释
processor it is an optional dependency
处理器，它是一个可选的依赖项
so don't forget to add optional true
所以不要忘记添加可选的true
here and so that that's basically
在这里，这基本上是
running as part of your compiler right
作为编译器的一部分运行
so it's only required by the compilation
所以只有编译需要
phase so it's going basically to look at
阶段，所以基本上要看一下
the source of your project and do
项目的来源并执行
something with it we'll see in a minute
一会儿我们会看到的
what it does on top of it but right now
它在它上面做什么，但现在
and it does is what we're going to
这就是我们要做的
showcase is it passes this additional
展示是否通过了这个额外的
metadata file validates it and then
元数据文件对其进行验证，然后
generate a file at a stone the location
在石头的位置生成文件
in your jar file in the Java of this
在您的Java的jar文件中
project actually and then the ID can
实际上是项目，然后ID可以
pick that for you right so first I'm
为您选择合适的，所以我首先
going to tell IntelliJ to import my
告诉IntelliJ导入我的
changes in the palm and in this Daniel
掌心和这丹尼尔的变化
should not be ready in 10 the burner
不应该在10个燃烧器中准备好
should not be read a lot great so what
不应该读太多，那又怎样
it reads now is we run the spring boot
它现在显示的是我们运行 spring boot
configuration annotation processor to
配置注释处理器
update the generated metadata so we're
更新生成的元数据，以便我们
going to do this rebuild the project the
要做这个重建项目
annotation processor will kick in now we
注释处理器将立即启动
are we still have that warning so we
我们还有警告吗？
need to run it once again and you can
需要再次运行它，您可以
actually now look at what the annotation
现在看一下注解
process of detail
详细过程
this is the resulting metadata the
这是产生的元数据
annotation process are now generated
现在生成注释过程
from our additional metadata where we
从我们的其他元数据中
specified some manual keys and manual
指定了一些手动键和手册
properties for those keys it doesn't
这些键没有的属性
look too different from what we just
看起来和我们刚才的太不同了
edited manually but maybe you'll notice
手动编辑，但也许您会注意到
already there is some other property
已经有其他财产了
hints here which is empty because we
提示这里是空的，因为我们
didn't specify any so something happened
没有指定任何内容，因此发生了一些事情
and now to close the circle or food
现在关闭圆圈或食物
counter property is not unknown property
柜台财产不是未知财产
in the IDE and at run time for spring
在IDE中并在春季运行时
would we get the same level of support
我们会得到同等水平的支持吗
we saw for the spring convict spring
我们看到了春天有罪的春天
boot configuration keys which come with
随附的启动配置键
spring good so we have a description we
春天很好，所以我们有一个描述我们
can specify all sorts of additional
可以指定各种其他
metadata we want to store in this key
我们要存储在此密钥中的元数据
and I can control click on that and it
我可以控制点击它
will actually take me to the metadata
实际上将带我进入元数据
declaration in my project because it
在我的项目中声明，因为它
knows that this is an additional key I
知道这是我的附加钥匙
specified in this very configuration
在此配置中指定
file so whenever I need to change
文件，所以每当我需要更改时
something that you can just control
你可以控制的东西
click there and continue editing the
单击此处并继续编辑
metadata right so far about the manual
到目前为止关于手册的元数据
metadata it sounds quite complicated but
元数据听起来很复杂，但
it actually isn't very complicated but
它实际上不是很复杂，但是
now Stefan will show you what you really
现在斯特凡会告诉你你真正的
want to do in your own projects right so
想在自己的项目中做正确的事
yeah the thing to remember here is of
是的，这里要记住的是
what yan just shown is this is a key
刚才显示的是这是一个关键
steam key right so I see that as if you
蒸汽键正确，所以我看到好像
have an application and you want to
有一个应用程序，你想
expose configuration keys or if you have
公开配置密钥，或者如果您有
if you have a library that you share
如果您有共享的图书馆
among several teams and you want to let
在几个团队之间，你想让
them know how they can use your app or
他们知道如何使用您的应用或
your library then you can expose those
你的图书馆，那么你可以揭露那些
metadata and as long as they use an ID
元数据，只要他们使用ID
that supports the metadata which they
支持他们所使用的元数据
all do now so there is support obviously
现在都做，所以显然有支持
in IntelliJ IDEA nest yes and in the
在IntelliJ IDEA中嵌套yes，然后在
bins now they can actually get live
垃圾箱，他们实际上可以活下来
documentation from your stuff so I want
从你的东西的文档，所以我想要
to extend that a little bit and to show
扩展一点并显示
you some new meta data that we've
您向我们提供了一些新的元数据
introduced a
介绍了
spring boot 103 the first one is int
spring boot 103第一个是int
okay I'm not on the right place in is
好吧，我不在正确的地方是
basically a way to provide additional
基本上是提供额外的方式
information about the key and there's
有关密钥的信息，还有
two things you can do with it you can
您可以用它做两件事
provide values so you already saw that
提供值，因此您已经看到了
with the with the demonstration with the
与演示与
hibernate DD a lot of lag and I can
使DD休眠很多滞后，我可以
provide the description and something
提供描述和一些东西
like this right and for the sake of the
这样的权利，为了
demo I'm going to add a new an extra
演示我要添加一个新的额外
value something like that right so if I
重视这样的权利，所以如果我
add that metadata then I get then I get
添加该元数据，然后我得到然后我得到
additional assistance in the ID
ID中的其他帮助
hopefully after any I need to make
希望以后我需要做
that's probably what I missed so you get
那可能就是我想念的，所以你得到了
the same auto completion as the one
与第一个相同的自动完成
you've sown earlier right but remember
您已经播种了，但是请记住
that's your own keys okay not the one in
那是你自己的钥匙好吧，不是一个
spring blue so the other thing I of
春天蓝色所以我的另一件事
course if I'm doing this then it's right
当然，如果我正在这样做，那是对的
now because I provided two values and I
现在，因为我提供了两个值，而我
didn't tell I did not provide it any
没告诉我我什么都没提供
extra information so what spring would
额外的信息，那么什么春天会
consider and IntelliJ IDEA considers is
考虑和IntelliJ IDEA认为是
that that's the list of values that this
那就是这的价值清单
key can hold and if you provide a value
键可以按住，如果您提供值
that's not in that list then that's not
那不在那个列表中那不是
a valid value I want to make sure that
我想确保一个有效值
any extra value can be provided so
可以提供任何额外的价值，以便
basically the list of values should be
基本上，值列表应该是
considered as special values that any
被视为任何
extra value might might do as well so
额外的价值可能也会这样做
for that i'm going to show you an extra
为此，我将向您展示一个额外的内容
feature which is called provider let's
称为提供者的功能
create that so provider is actually
创建那个提供者实际上是
special names that i'll see that are
我会看到的特殊名称是
providing in spring boot metadata 123 so
在春季引导元数据123中提供
we provide a list of official providers
我们提供官方供应商清单
and then the
然后
i D are supposed to pick that up and and
我应该拿起，然后
support auto-completion for those so
支持自动补全功能
these are the ones that we support for
这些是我们支持的
the moment so what I'm going to show you
那一刻，所以我要告诉你的是
now is any which means the value is just
现在是任何意味着值就是
a hint and any extra value will do
提示和任何额外的价值都可以
obviously it needs to be an integer but
显然，它必须是一个整数，但
any extra value will do so if I select
如果我选择任何额外的价值都可以
that and we dealt then my thing will go
那，我们处理，然后我的事会去
away right I can provide an extra value
马上我可以提供额外的价值
now you have time for year extracting we
现在您有时间提取我们
do right there okay so i want to show
就在那儿好吧，所以我想展示
you one more thing regarding extra
关于额外的一件事
metadata so for that let let me create
元数据，因此让我创建
an extra property let's say it's
一个额外的属性，假设它是
java.lang.string and i think that's it
java.lang.string，我认为就是这样
right it's good enough but let's see
对，这已经足够了，但让我们看看
that for some reason and many of you may
由于某些原因，你们中的许多人可能
have that this is actually not a simple
拥有这实际上不是简单的
string this is the name of a spring bean
字符串，这是Spring bean 的名称
for some reason you need to externalize
由于某些原因，您需要外部化
and we actually do in somewhat a
我们实际上在
configuration item you need to
您需要的配置项
externalize the name of the beam that's
外部化梁的名称
going to be used for whatever service so
将用于任何服务，所以
it would be nice instead of this roast
代替这种烧烤会很好
ring if you could get some assistance
如果可以得到帮助，请响
from the ID listing you all the beans
从ID列出您所有的beans
that are defined matching a certain type
定义为与某种类型匹配的
so that's what I'm going to do is I'm
所以这就是我要做的
going to create an extra int entry here
将在此处创建一个额外的int条目
i'm going to say football i'm going to
我要说足球我要去
say i'm on the provider and let's see
说我在提供者上，让我们看看
spring bean reference and that requires
春天 bean 参考，这需要
some parameters all that is described it
一些参数说明了一切
in in the described described in the
在描述的
documentation so you get full content
文档，以便您获取完整内容
assistance again so i'm going to say not
再次协助，所以我要说不
to confuse you let's say that i have two
让你困惑，我说我有两个
bins of type integer in my app I don't
我没有在应用中输入整数类型的垃圾箱
for the moment so let's do that
目前，让我们这样做
so being you should never do that by the
因此，您永远都不应这样做
way right a bit of type integer is
正确的整数类型的方式是
really bad don't do that
真的不好做
so I'm just adding those beans to my
所以我只是把那些 bean 加到我的
project okay so if i go to my
项目好吧，如果我去我的
configuration now or any configuration
现在配置或任何配置
that as this module as a dependency then
作为该模块的依赖项
i have auto completion again and i get
我又有自动完成功能，
this nice completion of the options that
选项的完美完成
are available to me and i also get full
对我可用，我也吃饱了
linking so i can basically go to the
链接，所以我基本上可以去
beam declaration I need to and again
我需要反复声明
refactoring is supported here as well so
这里也支持重构
if you're going to rename your being
如果你要重命名你的存在
that will pick up the new be named in
将会拿起新的名字
your configuration file yes it does I
您的配置文件是的
never try that that's the first time
永远不要尝试那是第一次
okay so solo for the manual metadata
好吧，单独使用手动元数据
that's all interesting and stuff but
那都是很有趣的东西，但是
it's it looks a bit advanced so I want
它看起来有点高级所以我想要
to step back a bit now you've seen what
现在退后一步，您已经看到了什么
happens behind the scenes and show you
发生在幕后，向你展示
the regular use case so the regular use
常规使用案例，所以常规使用
case is let's say that you have a ello
假设您有一个爱洛
service right so let's write it down
服务正确，所以让我们写下来
right now and you want to configure that
现在，您要配置
ello service let's flag that as a
ello服务让我们将其标记为
service you want to configure that with
您想要配置的服务
some properties so let's gather those
一些属性，让我们收集这些
into a file and let's create that file
进入文件，然后创建该文件
so I want to do two things I want to say
所以我想做两件事
I have a prefix for the ello message
我有ello消息的前缀
that's hello some Java doc and I won't
你好，一些Java文档，我不会
eat target so the thing to say ello to
吃目标所以要说好
and I'm not providing any value for that
我没有为此提供任何价值
I'll get up the Welcome message and I
我会收到欢迎消息，然后我
want to make sure its specified so I'm
要确保其指定，所以我
just going to add some constraint to it
只是要添加一些约束
okay so that's just a regular pojo
好的，那只是一个普通的pojo
there's nothing fancy about it but what
没什么好看的，但是
I'm going to add i'm going to add an
我要添加我要添加一个
extra property i'm going to say it's a
我会说这是一个额外的财产
configuration properties with a certain
具有一定的配置属性
prefix what that's going to do once you
给您添加前缀
enable that support in spring boot and
在Spring Boot中启用该支持，并
it's going to be able to map any key
它将能够映射任何键
well keys that are starting with the
井键以
yellow prix fixe to this beam so
黄色大奖赛固定到这束，所以
typically if in your configuration you
通常，如果在您的配置中
you say ello dot prefix it's going to
你说你好点前缀
call the set prefix method if you type
如果键入，则调用set前缀方法
ello target it will call the set target
ello目标它将调用设置的目标
without basically so the interesting
基本上没有那么有趣
part is this which is basically giving
这部分基本上是给
the namespace of the keys and after that
键的名称空间，之后
the properties are basically the name of
属性基本上是
the configuration key for that namespace
该名称空间的配置密钥
alright so if I go back to my service
好吧，如果我回到我的服务
now it's resolved so I'm going to do
现在解决了，所以我要去做
field injection I see that all is in the
现场注入我看到所有东西都在
back so is probably going to like that
回来所以大概会像那样
so no don't do feel the injection and
所以不要不觉得注射和
it's not listening to me you see that on
它不是在听我，你会看到
the recording I guess and let's say
我猜的录音，然后说
hello when the application starts right
你好，当应用程序启动正确
so let's say this not coding there
所以说这不在那里编码
that's not going to work is the property
那是行不通的是财产
is the prefix and property stop the
是前缀和属性stop
target so if i do that so i have a
目标，所以如果我这样做，那么我有一个
service that when it's initialized
服务在初始化时
inject the properties process them and
注入属性处理它们，
basically say hello which is not very
基本上打个招呼不是很好
interesting and we have our banner
有趣，我们有我们的旗帜
working here as you can see and for
如您所见，在这里工作
those who are following it it obviously
那些跟随它的人显然
should fail right because we never said
应该失败，因为我们从未说过
that we want to process that fine we
我们要处理得很好
never said do something with it right so
从来没有说对它做点什么，所以
for that i'm going to add an extra
为此，我要添加一个额外的
annotation on my configuration class i'm
我在配置类上的注释
going to say unable configuration
会说无法配置
properties and i'm going to specify the
属性，我要指定
name of the prop
道具名称
geez object there are other options or
geez对象还有其他选择或
for instance you can specify enabled
例如，您可以指定启用
configuration properties with without
不带配置属性
any argument and define your properties
任何参数并定义您的属性
object as components and there will be
对象作为组件，将有
picked up by component scanning
通过组件扫描拾取
automatically so if i do that again
自动，所以如果我再做一次
trust me if you can't read the exception
如果您看不懂例外，请相信我
message it's going to fail again because
消息将再次失败，因为
the value is not set so that's the
该值未设置，因此
validation issue yeah so let me put that
验证问题，是的，所以让我说一下
a bit a bit bigger for you rejected
稍大一点就被你拒绝了
value so target is none okay so let's
值，所以目标不行，所以让我们
let's give a value for that thing that
让我们为那个东西给一个价值
we have to write oh I have auto
我们必须写哦，我有自动
completion already okay so that's what
完成已经可以了，那就是
this annotation processor is primarily
这个注释处理器主要是
doing scanning your source code for pojo
扫描源代码中的pojo
annotated with configuration properties
带有配置属性的注释
and figuring out the kind of keys that
并弄清楚那种钥匙
are going to be exposed and looking at
将要暴露在外面，看着
the source code you can see that the
源代码，您可以看到
default value is taken you can see that
使用默认值，您可以看到
the Javadoc was taken away from the
Javadoc被从
field so this is really the standard use
字段，所以这实际上是标准用法
case you create a configuration
创建配置的情况
properties pojo you inject that into
属性注入你注入
whatever service you have and you add
无论您拥有什么服务，您都可以添加
the annotation processor to your project
项目的注释处理器
and basically you get complete auto
基本上你会得到完全自动
completion out of the box so let's say
开箱即用，所以说
something like that just prove that it
像这样的东西只是证明它
works so you should have some hello
可以，所以你应该打个招呼
world somewhere well that's a lot yeah
好地方的世界很多
that's probably the dirtiest there it is
那可能是那里最脏的
yeah okay right at all okay so that's
是的，好吧，好吧，那是
the kind of thing you can do very
你可以做的那种事情
quickly the the configuration the arky
快速配置方舟
you can use is very complete so you can
您可以使用的非常完整，因此您可以
do a bunch of stuff obviously I was a
做很多事情，显然我是一个
I'm a bit lazy for the sake of the demo
为了演示我有点懒
so I'm exposing to strengths which is
所以我要暴露的优点是
not really strongly typed but as young
打字不是很强，但是还很年轻
shown you whatever class whatever type
给你看什么班级什么类型
you expose it would be exposed in the
你暴露它会暴露在
meta meta data as well so if you expose
元元数据也是如此，如果您公开
a class
一类
of type foo then it will look for all
foo类型的，它将寻找所有
implementation of foo and autocomplete
foo和autocomplete的实现
the value directly there's nothing you
价值直接没有你
have to do know into right you just
必须知道你对吧
write your code as you would expect we
如您所愿，编写您的代码
generate the metadata for it and the
为它生成元数据
idee fixe set up so there's one problem
idee fixe设置好，所以有一个问题
with my configuration here is that
我的配置是
target is really a weird name so I want
目标真的是一个奇怪的名字，所以我想要
to use name instead and not target right
改用名字而不是正确的目标
so I'm going to create getters and
所以我要创建吸气剂和
setters for those and I'm going to say
这些的二传手，我要说的是
that these are deprecated because that
这些已被弃用，因为
was a bad decision we should have done
这是我们应该做的错误决定
that and just delegate to the new API
并委托给新的API
basically okay so far so good but the
到目前为止基本上还可以，但是
problem is i want i would like since i'm
问题是我想我想要我
basically managing so if someone is
基本上是这样管理的，如果有人
still using ello target it will still
仍在使用ello target它将仍然
work because the setter is still present
工作，因为二传手仍然存在
right but i want to let users know that
是的，但我想让用户知道
hello the target is no longer a very
你好，目标不再是一个非常
property and a world I want them to use
财产和我希望他们使用的世界
a load name that's the new property I
负载名称是我的新属性
want to them to use so what I'm going to
希望他们使用，所以我要
do is I'm going to add an extra
我要做的是添加一个额外的
annotation here from spring boot with a
从 spring boot 注释这里
reason and a replacement right and if I
原因和更换权，如果我
built did I do it no I didn't so if i
内置我做了吗不，如果我不这样做
built and i go back to my config then
建立，然后回到我的配置
ello target is deprecated and i can see
ello目标已弃用，我可以看到
right away why it's deprecated okay and
立即为什么不赞成使用
as you would expect then you have the
如您所愿，那么您拥有
magic replacement so that works also
魔术替换，所以也可以
declaratively from your code so yeah
从您的代码中声明地
that's really the real use case you
那才是真正的用例
should use it starts with that stuff so
应该使用它开头的东西，所以
designing your API designing new
设计您的API设计新
configuration properties and let the
配置属性，然后
spring boot configuration processor
弹簧启动配置处理器
generate the metadata automatically for
自动为生成元数据
you right so let's switch to
你说的对，所以我们切换到
some quite different topic since we
自从我们有了一些完全不同的话题
spent quite some time but I think it's
花了很多时间，但我认为是
important to understand how these
重要的是要了解这些
configuration keys can work and how you
配置键可以工作，以及您如何工作
can create your own configuration
可以创建自己的配置
universe for your application or
您的应用程序的Universe或
services let's actually talk about how
服务让我们实际讨论一下
to run and/or debug your spring boot
运行和/或调试Spring Boot
applications there is a special run
应用程序有一个特殊的运行
configuration type for spring mood
春季心情的配置类型
applications we saw that after creating
应用程序，我们看到创建后
this template project with spring
这个模板项目与春天
initializer it automatically created
自动创建的初始化程序
this run configuration and the way it
运行配置及其方式
works is that any module containing
起作用的是，任何包含
exactly one spring good application
恰好是一个春季的好应用
class will be considered to be a
该课程将被视为
standalone springwood application
独立的弹性木应用
microservice whatever you call it and
无论您叫什么微服务，
corresponding run configuration will be
相应的运行配置将是
created automatically for you so you can
为您自动创建，因此您可以
just go ahead and run it just have to
只是继续运行就可以了
specify the main class vm options
指定主类的vm选项
program arguments whatever and then
程序参数什么然后
comes the interesting part the
有趣的部分
specialization for running spring mood
春运专攻
applications so that's this part here we
应用程序，所以这是我们的一部分
can just with a single checkbox enable
只需启用一个复选框即可
debug output by default that's another
默认情况下调试输出
argument you could pass on the comment
你可以传递评论的论点
line to spring dude but you can use this
行到春天花花公子，但你可以用这个
checkbox here people who don't like the
勾选此处不喜欢的人
spring boot banner or your own banner
spring boot 横幅或您自己的横幅
can hide it with the check box as well I
也可以用复选框将其隐藏
won't click because I think you re
不会点击，因为我认为你是
really hates me for building your
真的恨我建立你的
feature and the real interesting thing
功能和真正有趣的事情
is now this little table over right
现在是这张小桌子了吗
parameters so what does it do we have
参数，所以我们有什么用
our configuration files with keys and
我们的配置文件，包含密钥和
values so if you encounter some problem
值，所以如果您遇到问题
or you want to test a you want to run an
或者您想测试一个您想运行一个
a/b test or some kind of variation of
a / b测试或某种形式的变化
your configuration you would need to
您的配置，您将需要
modify your configuration file or you
修改您的配置文件
would have to create a profile of this
将不得不为此创建一个配置文件
configuration file and run with that
配置文件并运行
profile but it's much easier just to
个人资料，但只需
overwrite selected keys with a different
用其他覆盖所选键
value
值
and just for the run time so we don't
只是在运行时，所以我们不
have to modify the source code this is
必须修改源代码，这是
ide specific metadata it won't get
ide它不会得到的特定元数据
stored in your source repository unless
存储在您的源存储库中，除非
you tell it to do it so i can add
你告诉它这样做，所以我可以添加
additional configuration keys I have
我拥有的其他配置密钥
full auto completion here as well just
全自动完成以及
like in the config file so maybe I want
就像在配置文件中一样，也许我想要
to change the banner multiple the port
更改横幅多个端口
yeah let's change the port to server
是的，让我们将端口更改为服务器
port and let's maybe change it to what
端口，让我们将其更改为
you change you want to change my Daniel
你改变你想改变我的丹尼尔
again yeah no I don't want to change it
再次是，不，我不想更改它
again ranked you okay let's change the
再次给您排名，让我们更改
year server port we want to run to 8000
要运行到8000年的服务器端口
one maybe and as you can see in the
一个也许，就像你在
first column lists this check box
第一列列出了此复选框
enabled so why is that here we can
启用，为什么在这里我们可以
quickly enable and disable overriding
快速启用和禁用覆盖
parameters to just switch between
仅在两个参数之间切换的参数
different configurations more or less on
不同的配置或多或少
the fly without doing something else and
不用做其他事情的苍蝇
just unchecking and check box the other
只是取消选中并选中另一个
thing you can easily do is to create a
您可以轻松地做的是创建一个
copy of an existing one configuration
现有一个配置的副本
and modify it with some parameters and
并使用一些参数对其进行修改，
then you can run whatever version of
那么您可以运行任何版本的
your app you want to run with different
您想要与其他应用一起运行的应用
overriding parameters so when we run
覆盖参数，所以当我们运行
this now and by the way IntelliJ knows
现在和IntelliJ知道的方式
that this application is already running
该应用程序已经在运行
and we'll ask you to stop and rerun it
我们会请您停止并重新运行
so you don't end up with two instances
所以你不会有两个实例
obably which wouldn't work it could be
显然这是行不通的
changed before because we change the
之前更改过，因为我们更改了
port yeah that was my AE so when we go
是的，那是我的AE，所以当我们走时
to 8001 it works right
到8001正常
ok I think that's the stuff about the
好的，我认为这是关于
run configuration we have some more
运行配置，我们还有更多
things in the plants but I think this is
植物中的东西，但我认为这是
a nice and easy way to quickly tune your
快速方便地调优您的好方法
application and just debug it with some
应用程序，然后用一些调试
different properties ok so you know the
不同的属性好，所以你知道
other thing that you can do is sew a
您可以做的另一件事是缝制
spring boot is a profile management so
Spring Boot是一个配置文件管理，因此
by default spring boot is actually going
默认情况下，Spring Boot实际上正在运行
to read any application dash the name of
读取任何应用程序的破折号
the profile when it's enabled so let's
个人资料启用后，让我们
create a des profile here and for the
在此处并为
depth of the sake of the death profile
死亡概况的深度
i'm going to say security i'm going to
我要说的是安全性
disable security all together right what
一起禁用安全功能
I'm going also to do is in my demo app
我还要在演示应用程序中做
I'm going to create a beam let's quickly
我要创建一个光束，让我们快速
create a controller which only is
创建一个仅
enabled with profile def it used to be
使用配置文件def启用它曾经是
actually auto configuration for the h2
实际上是h2的自动配置
console if you know that but since dense
控制台，如果你知道，但由于密集
we have auto configuration support for
我们有自动配置支持
it so I can't show that anymore and
它，所以我不能再显示了，
instead I can show you the most useful
相反，我可以向您展示最有用的
controller ever right I think that's
控制器永远正确，我认为那是
really really nice link to string there
真的很不错的链接到那里的字符串
ok so if i if i go here likely the young
好吧，如果我去的话我可能会年轻
shown already i can say oh no I want
已经显示我可以说哦，不，我想要
what I want to do instead is I want to
我想做的是
have to run configurations so I want to
必须运行配置，所以我想
have one for development and one for
有一个发展，一个为
whatever other profile i wanna use so
我想使用的其他任何个人资料
i'm going to use the copy a run config
我将使用复制运行配置
here and and simply just say that I want
在这里，只是说我想要
the death profile right let's say I
正确的死亡档案让我说
don't want that instead so if i run
不想那样，所以如果我跑步
again I should get whatever for the sake
再说一遍我应该得到什么
of the demo right its most a spring
演示的最春天
feature but oh yeah for one I should not
功能，但哦，是的，我不应该
have any
有什么
security in place and my debug thing is
安全到位，我的调试工作是
available right not super interesting
可用的权利不是超级有趣
unless that for some reason you want you
除非出于某种原因你想要你
want to rename that profile and if you
要重命名该个人资料，如果您
do with the usual shortcut then IntelliJ
使用通常的快捷方式，然后IntelliJ
IDEA will actually detect that you have
IDEA实际上会检测到您有
a spring boot configuration for that
一个 spring boot 配置
profile and it will basically offer you
个人资料，它将基本上为您提供
to rename the file as well right okay we
重命名文件，好吧，我们
looked at spring boot specific stuff we
看了 spring boot 的具体内容
are now going to make a short excursion
现在要进行短暂的游览
into a bit more general spring features
变成更一般的弹簧特征
in IntelliJ I'm sorry
在IntelliJ中，对不起
no it doesn't yet good question but it
不，这不是一个好问题，但是
will be possible yeah usually you don't
是可能的，通常你不会
rename your profile every day so it
每天重命名您的个人资料
should be hopefully quite safe but good
希望应该很安全但是很好
catch right going to some more general
赶上去一些更一般
stuff how can you navigate your spring
东西，你该如何度过春天
application in IntelliJ IDEA so we have
IntelliJ IDEA中的应用程序，所以我们有
spring good application annotation which
春天不错的应用注释
is a matter annotation it includes a
是事项注释，它包括一个
component scan for the current package
组件扫描当前程序包
it includes a configuration annotation
它包含一个配置注释
so we have this little icon here which
所以我们在这里有这个小图标
allows us to navigate to the actual
允许我们导航到实际
means or the controllers which have been
手段或控制者已经
created due to this configuration so
由于此配置而创建，因此
that's very easy to navigate for from
这很容易从中导航
this application for example to the
这个应用程序例如
debug controller which is snowing the
下雪的调试控制器
same file but otherwise it would open
相同的文件，否则它将打开
the corresponding class for us and we
我们和我们对应的班级
can also do the way back so I can
也可以回去，所以我可以
navigate to the declaring configuration
导航到声明配置
using the same mechanism and now
现在使用相同的机制
declares a jump to demo application
声明跳转到演示应用程序
which is actually the configuration
这实际上是配置
responsible for creating this rest
负责创建此休息
controller which is linked below there
链接在下面的控制器
is a somewhat related feature which is
是有点相关的功能
very powerful it's called navigate
功能非常强大，称为导航
related symbol and what that does is
相关符号，它的作用是
really context-dependent it actually
确实取决于上下文
works in other frameworks or other
在其他框架或其他框架中工作
technologies as well and it provides
技术，它提供
some kind of nip semantic navigation so
某种nip语义导航
for example in spring MVC you have your
例如在春季MVC中，您拥有
controller and you have your view and
控制器，您有自己的看法和
IntelliJ understands the relation
IntelliJ了解关系
between those two and offers you to
在这两个之间，并为您提供
navigate between those two by using this
使用此在这两个之间导航
function related symbol and the same
功能相关的符号和相同
thing can work for navigating from the
事情可以从中导航
configuration file to the beans and
配置文件到bean和
another use case which is again
另一个用例又是
springwood specific when you are in your
当您在自己的状态时，使用Springwood专用
occasion properties file and you want to
场合属性文件，你想
go to the metadata file your additional
转到元数据文件
metadata file you wrote you can use the
您编写的元数据文件可以使用
same shortcut you navigate related
与您浏览相关的相同快捷方式
symbol and it will open the additional
符号，它将打开其他
JSON files or one shortcut to ruin and
JSON文件或一种破坏和删除文件的快捷方式
many many navigation possibilities in
中的许多导航可能性
spring and spring MVC and grails it
春季和春季MVC并获得成功
works in many frameworks actually so we
实际上可以在许多框架中工作，所以我们
use some navigation from an already
使用已经存在的导航
opened editor to some related stuff
打开一些相关内容的编辑器
there's another shortcut which is very
还有另一个捷径
powerful to navigate to anything from
强大的导航能力，从
anywhere so if i want to find bean by
任何地方，所以如果我想找beans
name i can use a shortcut it's called a
我可以使用快捷方式命名为
go-to symbol and that includes spring
转到符号，其中包括弹簧
beans so i should be able to find the
bean ，所以我应该能够找到
debug controller here and i can jump
在这里调试控制器，我可以跳
there so if you can even only guess
在那里，如果你甚至只能猜测
parts of the name it will also match
名称的一部分也将匹配
with better matching and camera case
搭配更好的相机套
matching be names and propose them in
匹配名称并在其中提出建议
this completion pop up and you can
此完成弹出，您可以
quickly go to any bean definition from
快速从以下位置转到任何bean定义
anywhere just wherever you are okay
无论您在哪里都可以
there's another possibility to explore
还有另一种探索的可能性
what is happening spring wise in your
在你的春天明智的是什么
application and that's the spring tool
应用程序，这就是spring tool
window below here so what it does is it
这下面的窗口是做什么的
shows all the file sets which are more
显示所有更多的文件集
or less a representation of your spring
或更少代表你的春天
application contexts pure module we can
应用程序上下文纯模块，我们可以
also join all modules if you don't want
如果不想的话，也可以加入所有模块
to group them by module we can also
按模块分组，我们也可以
disable different facets so you can put
禁用不同的方面，以便您可以放
all beans on one big list if you rather
如果愿意，所有 bean 都列在一个大列表中
prefer that and what you see here is a
喜欢那个，你在这里看到的是
quite long list of auto configuration
自动配置的清单很长
classes which have been triggered due to
由于以下原因触发的课程
the springboard application which
跳板的应用
enables auto configuration so these are
启用自动配置，因此这些
all the auto configuration classes which
所有的自动配置类
spring would automatically adds to just
春天会自动添加到
bring good application in this case and
在这种情况下带来良好的应用
we should also find our debug controller
我们还应该找到我们的调试控制器
in here
在这里
emo application and those are all the
emo应用程序，这些都是
beans which are configured by our demo
由我们的演示配置的bean
application I can use click search here
我可以使用的应用程序单击此处搜索
and quickly navigate to the debug
并快速导航到调试
controller again so that's another way
控制器再次，这是另一种方式
to access beans and to understand the
访问bean并了解
structure of your configuration and do
您的配置结构并执行
resulting beans on the right you can see
您可以在右边看到生成的 bean
some meta information we can see that
一些元信息，我们可以看到
it's a controller beam we see the source
这是一个控制器光束，我们看到了光源
and we even see that this is limited to
我们甚至看到这仅限于
the profile development so it just being
配置文件的发展，所以它只是
will only be available in that profile
仅在该个人资料中可用
right so another last thing for
对，所以还有另一件事
navigation is actually i'm going to
导航实际上是我要去的
reset to selection so it actually works
重置为选择，以便它实际起作用
there's a very powerful shortcut which
有一个非常强大的快捷方式
is called select in and what that does
称为“选择进入”，它的作用是
is take the element your cursor is on
是采用光标所在的元素
and provide your navigation targets
并提供您的导航目标
mostly to windows where you actually
大多到您实际所在的窗户
want to select that very element you are
想选择您就是那个元素
in null and that works for spring beans
为null，适用于Spring bean
as well so alt f1 and I get a list of
以及alt f1和我得到的列表
tool windows which are available as
工具窗口可作为
navigation targets and one of them is
导航目标，其中之一是
spring beans tool window so if I select
Spring bean 工具窗口，所以如果我选择
that it will select the corresponding
它将选择相应的
file set the corresponding configuration
文件设置相应的配置
and select the debug controller for me
并为我选择调试控制器
and I can go there and see what is
我可以去那里看看是什么
related to that bean what our beans are
与那个 bean 有关我们的 bean 是什么
in this context in this configuration so
在这种情况下，在这种配置下
that's a very nice and quick way to open
这是一种非常好的快捷方法
the spring beans view right from the
Spring bean 从
current beam from the current
从当前电流
configuration ok that is all good but
配置还可以，但是很好
old and I'm going to show you something
老了，我要给你看一些东西
which is very new during you get every
在您获得每一个时，这都是很新的
new like last night like like last back
像昨晚一样，像过去一样
here no it has been there for a few
这里不，它已经去过那里了
weeks but it has mostly gone unnoticed
几周，但它几乎没有被注意
apparently so far in the community and I
到目前为止，在社区和我看来
think this is one of the most
认为这是最
interesting new features
有趣的新功能
for spring development in general in the
一般用于春季开发
upcoming 15 version and so we solve
即将发布的15版本，因此我们解决了
navigating beans right I showed you a
导航 bean 吧，我给你看了一个
few ways how to do that and it's all
几种方法来做到这一点
nice and easy to use but some spring
不错，易于使用，但是有些春天
applications suffer from a quite complex
应用程序非常复杂
or complicated and sometimes a bit
或复杂，有时会有点
non-managed setup of their configuration
其配置的非托管设置
so when you join a new project or you
所以当您加入一个新项目或
have new hires and they really have
有新员工，他们确实有
trouble figuring out what is the
麻烦弄清楚是什么
structure of your spring configuration
Spring 配置的结构
context where does this being come from
这是从哪里来的
why is it there how are these
为什么会有这些
configuration files for example related
配置文件，例如相关
to each other and we thought about this
彼此，我们考虑了一下
and we came up with an idea to show a
我们想到了一个展示
graph of the actual configuration
实际配置图
happening in your application so this is
发生在您的应用程序中，所以这是
a real synthetic project it does not
一个真正的综合项目，它没有
have any meaning it's just for
有什么意思
demonstration purposes and so you invoke
演示目的，所以您调用
diagrams show diagram and yes the new
图显示图，是新的
diagram type spring model dependencies
图类型弹簧模型依赖性
so let's maximize this a bit
所以让我们最大化它
so what this shows is on the left the
所以这显示在左边
module node then we have to 5 sets here
模块节点，那么我们必须在这里设置5套
or to created context and then it shows
或创建上下文，然后显示
the main configuration files for example
主要配置文件例如
B dot XML yeah just for completeness of
B点XML是的，仅出于完整性考虑
course nobody is going to use Excel
当然没有人要使用Excel
anymore but as you can see there are
不再，但正如您所看到的
different shapes and different errors
不同形状和不同误差
and colors here visualizing the
和颜色在这里可视化
relationship between all those
所有这些之间的关系
configuration files so for example if
配置文件，例如
you have imports if you have components
你有进口如果你有组件
gains which in turn trigger another set
增益又触发另一组
of configuration beans you would really
您将真正配置的bean
have a hard time to understand those
很难理解那些
relations by just looking at the code or
通过查看代码或
by just guessing what this components
通过猜测这个组成部分
gain might trigger might not trigger in
增益可能触发可能不会触发
at one time so I think this is a very
一次，所以我认为这是一个非常
nice possibility to actually see what
实际看到什么的可能性很大
your spring configuration does you can
你的Spring 配置可以吗
also see quite some problems we have a
也看到很多问题，我们有一个
couple of red edges here which show
几个红色的边缘在这里显示
cycles or configuration properties
周期或配置属性
configuration problems we have a couple
配置问题，我们有几个
of tooltips here showing where this
这里的工具提示显示了
relation is actually defined I can
关系实际上是可以定义的
select this node press f4 and go to that
选择此节点，按f4并转到
exact location in your configuration
您配置中的确切位置
file via XML watch our config and you
通过XML文件观看我们的配置，您
will get to the exact point triggering
将到达确切的点触发
this relationship we saw on the graph so
我们在图表上看到的这种关系
I think that's a very powerful feature
我认为这是一个非常强大的功能
to understand what is happening behind
了解背后发生了什么
the scenes how your setup is actually
场景实际上是如何设置的
structured or not structured and you can
结构化或非结构化，您可以
use this graph to verify that your
使用此图来验证您的
configuration is what you actually
配置实际上是您的实际配置
expect it to be net application runtime
期望它是网络应用程序运行时
this is all good a new new we are
这都是新的好东西，我们是
thinking about a few additions to that
考虑一些补充
so stay tuned we are thinking about
所以请继续关注我们在考虑
stuff like refactoring configuration
诸如重构配置之类的东西
setups like moving imports between
诸如在之间移动导入的设置
different files automatically for you
自动为您提供不同的文件
using this graph we can just use
使用这个图我们可以使用
drag-and-drop and change spring
拖放并改变弹簧
configuration for you and generate the
为您配置并生成
corresponding code needed for changing G
更改G所需的相应代码
set up so I think this will really help
设置，所以我认为这真的有帮助
to structure applications and understand
构造应用程序并了解
whatever was or has been configured in
曾经或曾经配置过的
the last few years in bigger
在过去的几年中
applications well I guess we are done
应用程序很好，我想我们已经完成了
with our demo here and we'll be happy to
通过我们的演示，我们很乐意
take questions yep any question don't be
是的，是的，没有问题
shy please
请害羞
no question I'm sorry
毫无疑问，我很抱歉
no actually the graph is based on the
实际上，该图不是基于
spring facet configuration in your
您的春季构面配置
application so we didn't show that we
应用程序，所以我们没有表明我们
have here a facet with a couple of five
这边有几个面
sets and they have some main
集，他们有一些主要
configuration files and all the rest of
配置文件以及所有其他
the graph which also nicely demonstrates
该图也很好地展示了
the power is actually triggered by those
力量实际上是由那些
main entry point configurations right so
主入口点配置正确，所以
as soon as long as you have the spring
只要你有春天
fest set up in place it will just use
巨星建立就可以使用
that data I actually missed one thing
我实际上错过了一件事的数据
which is the same thing works actually
实际上是一样的东西
for spring boot so there is quite a
对于 spring boot ，所以有一个
magic with spring boot and auto
弹簧启动和自动魔术
configuration right I mean we saw this
配置正确，我是说我们看到了
long list of other configurations which
其他配置的长列表
have been shown in the spring beans
已经显示在Spring bean 中
explorer and i'm just going to trigger
资源管理器，我将要触发
this diagram in spring mood application
此图在春季心情应用中
so this is
所以这是
the basic setup of our application right
我们的应用程序权限的基本设置
very easy to understand nothing to worry
很容易理解，不用担心
about and that's beauty of spring root
关于，这就是春天的根源之美
in my opinion so there's there's not
我认为没有
much to worry about and usually most
通常要担心的很多
bring good applications you won't have a
带来好的应用程序，您将不会
much more complex graph than what we see
比我们看到的要复杂得多的图
right here at least not per module or
在这里至少不是每个模块或
per micro service right so things become
每个微服务的权利，所以事情变得
different when I switch on configuration
开启配置时有所不同
nodes which are not located in the
不位于
project but in libraries so coming from
项目，但在图书馆，所以来自
spring would automatically and this is
春天会自动，这是
actually the full graph or a set limited
实际上是完整图或有限集合
set of the auto configuration graph
自动配置图的集合
which spring boot will trade at one time
哪个 spring boot 可以一次交易
for me right so this is quite impressive
对我来说这非常令人印象深刻
and this is basically the magic behind
这基本上就是背后的魔力
spring mood and the auto configuration
春天的心情和自动配置
as you can see the Springwood
如您所见，斯普林伍德
application note triggers a quite
应用笔记触发了
impressive list of other configuration
其他配置令人印象深刻的清单
classes which in turn import another set
依次导入另一组的类
of configuration classes and whatnot so
配置类，什么都不是
this is a nice visualization of what
这是一个很好的可视化内容
spring auto configuration actually does
弹簧自动配置实际上确实
at runtime and nice possibility for you
在运行时，您的可能性很大
to understand why some all the
了解为什么所有这些
configuration is actually not dare even
配置实际上甚至都不敢
if you're expecting maybe you choose the
如果您期望的话，可以选择
wrong jar or long dependency or you
错误的jar或长期依赖关系，或者您
forgot to set some flag and we are
忘了设置一些标志，我们是
working very hard to really show the
努力工作才能真正展现出
actual graph that will be used at one
实际使用的图形
time you can switch on debugging as we
时间，您可以打开调试，因为我们
saw when Stefan was switching the debug
看到Stefan何时切换调试
level to show what springwood actually
水平显示弹簧木实际上是什么
does with auto configuration because
使用自动配置，因为
there's quite a few conditions that
有很多条件
apply to enable or disable specific auto
申请启用或禁用特定的自动
configurations but we really strive to
配置，但我们确实努力做到
have the same view here on this graph so
在此图上的视图相同
you can see you what your application
你可以看到你的应用程序
will do at runtime without actually
将在运行时实际执行
starting and debugging it in the run
在运行中启动和调试
configuration
组态
it is yeah no no this is a spring
是的，不，不，这是春天
supporters only in the paid edition of
支持者仅在付费版本中
IntelliJ yeah it's in the paper or
IntelliJ是的，它在纸上或
ammonia yes it does support web Syria it
氨水是的，它确实支持网络叙利亚
was a question in the back yeah thanks
是后面的一个问题，是的，谢谢
we are thinking about that yeah basic
我们正在考虑基本的
the question was is there some kind of
问题是是否存在某种
legend for this graph right there is a
此图的图例右边有一个
twit appear which shows you what this is
twit出现，向您显示这是什么
and what the trigger so for this
以及触发的原因是什么
specific note it shows the number of
具体说明显示数量
important resources for configuration
配置重要资源
classes we will show the number of
类，我们将显示
actually linked beans so we have all
实际上链接了beans，所以我们都有
this information we are still thinking
这些信息我们还在思考
of what kind of information is really
到底是什么样的信息
necessary or useful on this graph and
此图上必要或有用的，以及
maybe some kind of property table might
也许某种属性表可能
be a good solution so you can actually
是一个很好的解决方案，这样您就可以
cycle through those nodes and inspect
遍历这些节点并检查
him more for so yeah something like that
他更多的是这样的
might be coming welcome yes
可能会来欢迎
mm-hmm
毫米-毫米
yeah so the question is will application
是的，所以问题是申请
Yama config file support be on par with
Yama配置文件支持与
application to property support yes we
申请财产支持是的，我们
are going to try it it's a bit more
将要尝试它的更多
difficult than having the same support
比得到相同的支持困难
on application properties because yamel
在应用程序上的特性，因为yamel
is a bit more complex by itself but we
本身就比较复杂，但是我们
really want to have a decent support in
真的很想在
the upcoming version 15 yeah okay when i
即将发布的版本15是的，当我
try to what oh you can actually print it
尝试到什么您可以实际打印它
here you can actually also export it as
在这里，您实际上也可以将其导出为
a PNG or SVG file so that's very nice
一个PNG或SVG文件，所以非常好
and handy if you want to have to a big
方便，如果您想
wall of spring madness in your project
您的项目中的疯狂之墙
office yeah this is actually the full
是的，这实际上是完整的
configuration graph yeah what I just
配置图是的，我只是
showed you in the screen boot demo
在屏幕启动演示中向您展示了
application was a limited set we already
应用程序是一个有限的设置，我们已经
filter some of the other configurations
过滤其他一些配置
by the conditions that applied order to
根据适用于订单的条件
those auto configurations this is
这些自动配置是
actually the maximum of auto
实际上是自动的最大值
configurations you can get in springwood
您可以在Springwood中获得的配置
it has all the dependencies of
它具有以下所有依赖性
springwood one of three and everything
斯普林伍德三和一切之一
you clear everything and everything you
你清除所有的一切
could get for free yeah that might be
可以免费获得，是的
another feature to filter groups out to
另一个功能可以过滤出分组
limit the graph by some set of flags
通过一组标志限制图形
whatever yeah okay so if you want to
好的，如果你想
discuss a bit more with us though they
尽管他们与我们讨论了更多
need do not hesitate thanks a lot yeah
需要不要犹豫，谢谢
thank you very much
非常感谢你
you
您